{"data":[{"question":"Our manufacturer's carelessness ___ our difficulties.","a":"was adding to","b":"added to","c":"will be added to","d":"had added to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The World War II ___ in 1939.","a":"broke out","b":"was broken out","c":"was happened","d":"was broken","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + active voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"As the time went on, his theory ___ to be wrong.","a":"is proved","b":"proved","c":"was proved","d":"is to prove","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (The Simple Past can be used with a duration which starts and stops in the past) + active voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"It is said that the music hall can ___ 1,000 people.","a":"be seated","b":"seat","c":"takes","d":"costs","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Active voice \n- Seat: if a place seats a number of people, it has enough seats for that number","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The baby is about ___ and can't ___by himself.","a":"5-month-old, be left","b":"5 months old, leave","c":"5-month old, leave","d":"5 months old, be left","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 5 months od= His year old is 5 month\n- We often say \"five-month-year old\n- Passive voice with \"can\" : can + be + pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"These young men ___ our volleyball team.","a":"are belonged to","b":"are belong to","c":"belongs to","d":"belong to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Belong to(Verb): if something belongs to someone, they own it \n- Subject is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"One of the girls ___ while playing basketball.","a":"were hurting","b":"hurt","c":"had been hurt","d":"got hurt","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get hurt (hurt is adjective in this case)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Lincoln ___ by many as a friend of freedom.","a":"is thought of","b":"is thought","c":"is thinking of","d":"thinks of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Think of: to remember something \n- Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The reporter wanted ___ the head of the group, but it was impossible.","a":"to be seen","b":"to see","c":"being to see","d":"seeing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Want + to verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Those short stories ___ again.","a":"are worthy reading","b":"are worth to read","c":"are worth reading","d":"are worth being read","answer":"3","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}